Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Tonight, so-called
magician Lionel shrike
is making another sad
attempt for attention
by performing what he calls
an impossible feat.
The safe is made of
the strongest iron.
It can't be sawed
through or pried.
Yet, Lionel shrike thinks
he's able to escape.
Dad! Dad!
Hey, buddy.
You made it, huh?
Now, see that seat there?
Is Lionel shrike
the kind of magician
who can pull this off?
Or is he actually
in over his head?
We'll see about that.
What's the matter?
I don't want you to go.
Dylan, come on.
We talked about this.
Remember?
This is what I do.
I got to prove all
those naysayers wrong.
Okay? Besides...
I always keep
something up my sleeve.
Now, got your watch
like your dad's?
Okay. How many seconds?
300.
300. Maybe a few less.
Mmm.
I love you so much.
Okay.
See you later, big man.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
- Lionel shrike!
Will he be able
to hold his breath?
Will he be able to
somehow escape the safe?
Three, two, one...
Two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight...
296...
297, 298, 299, 300.
303, 304...
It's five minutes now,
and we have not
seen or heard anything
from Lionel shrike yet.
Move!
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Let go of me!
Dad!
No! Dad!
Dad! Let go!
Find him!
The eye.
It may not lie...
But don't think for a moment
that it can't be lied to.
Seeing is believing.
But is it truth?
People see the horsemen
as noble Robin hoods.
Are they?
Or are they common thieves?
Depends on your point of view.
They robbed a bank in Paris
from a stage in las Vegas.
They fleeced
an insurance magnate
of hundreds of
millions of dollars
and disappeared from
a roof in New York.
Always showering their
devoted fans with money.
Here's what you don't know.
They left one man behind.
Framed. Holding the bag.
Me.
Are you listening, horsemen?
When you emerge,
and you will...
I will be there waiting.
Because mark my words,
you will get
what's coming to you.
In ways you can't expect.
But very much deserve.
Because one thing
I believe in
is any eye for an eye.
Welcome, Daniel atlas.
Who am I speaking to?
I asked to see the face
behind all of this.
You've asked many questions.
And registered
many complaints.
You can rest assured
that we've heard you.
Have you? Because I don't...
Trust?
No.
Your leader?
Your fellow horsemen?
I don't like
that we've been living
in hiding for a year.
I don't like
that every message
i get from Dylan is,
"wait. Be patient.
"The eye has a plan."
Wait. Be patient.
The eye has a plan.
This is games and
it's not working for me.
You feel it is you
who should be leading
the horsemen,
not Dylan.
If that is
what you desire,
stay the course.
Trust that
your unique talents
and remarkable mind
will not go unrecognized.
We have a new mission
for the horsemen.
Dylan has a plan
and will gather
you together soon.
Now leave!
...north Carolina,
Florida, Maryland, Maine.
We're talking the entire
eastern seaboard.
I need to see some results.
Oh, hey. Oh, sorry.
Just real quick.
Can I have you for
a couple of minutes?
I'm right in the middle
of something, Dylan.
No, I know. It's okay.
Hey. Hey, everybody. Sorry.
Sorry about that.
Call the mayor.
Thanks a lot.
Twins, huh? Good.
Is he coming?
Look, I wouldn't
have brought you
out of that meeting
unless it was
something important.
It's about
the horsemen.
Something's happening here
and it's happening now.
Message boards.
Elite magic society.
There is chatter going on
about the horsemen
and something happening
with octa, the giant
software company.
I know what octa is.
I'm sorry, ma'am,
but two months ago
we sent men
to Philadelphia
because he knew...
And I said
that I was wrong.
He knew that
the horsemen
were going to hit
the euro-Atlantic
banking summit.
I have proof.
Let him talk.
Thank you.
Communications.
Contact between who I think
might be Daniel atlas
and who may be
merritt mckinney.
And what do you have?
Emails? Cell phones?
Any transcripts?
Pigeons.
What?
I'm sorry,
you mean stool pigeons?
No, I mean
actual pigeon pigeons.
Like carrier pigeons.
Okay? Magicians work
with pigeons.
Doves.
Stay with me.
This pigeon,
right here...
There's Daniel atlas.
Same pigeon.
East village.
Same pigeon, west village.
42nd street, pigeon.
65th street.
All the way up to the
George Washington bridge
on a sail boat
with a guy
that looks just
like merritt mckinney.
And what does
this all mean?
I know
what it means.
It means nothing.
It's bullshit.
Could you
sing a new song?
No.
How is it that
two years ago
you were so close...
You think I went
out of my way to screw up
my own investigation?
But you want everybody
else to think that
you're an idiot.
Okay, stop.
Cowan, I know I'm new here,
but as far as I can tell,
people who don't
even know you,
think you're an asshole.
You don't know me,
but my first year
in the academy,
you gave a talk.
The "long game"
you called it.
You talked about
a moral compass.
About how you believed
in yours immutably.
And I thought to myself,
"that guy.
"One day,
i want to be that guy."
And now... a pigeon?
Technically, it was
a few pigeons, but I hear
what you're saying.
Okay.
So here's what
I'm going to do.
You want to take
a vacation day?
But I'm not going
to devote resources
to another snipe hunt.
I came to clean this mess up,
not add to it. I'm sorry.
Boss, thank you.
I promise you,
it won't be a snipe hunt.
We're gonna get
those horsemen.
She's great.
The problem is
when you're two people
at the same time,
one of them is bound
to trip the other.
And when that happens,
I will be there.
Duly noted.
Oh. Hi!
Who are you?
What are you doing in my...
It's actually
a funny story.
How did you get
into my apartment?
Whoa!
I think it's funny.
It's not like funny "ha ha."
Or you might not think
that it's funny "ha ha."
I think it's funny.
I guess it's all
kind of relative.
I was actually...
No, that's not...
I made myself in
the neighborhood
and now I'm here,
and maybe...
Okay.
Seriously,
how did you
get in here?
Are you some kind
of crazed fan
or something?
Oh, my god.
No, no, no,
i recognize you.
You did that b-grade
"geek magic" thing,
didn't you?
You pulled a...
Pulled a hat
out of the rabbit.
A hat out of the rabbit,
that's right.
I know
that it didn't work.
No, it was actually
kind of disgusting.
Well, your drop was obvious
and your body shell is flimsy.
So if you wouldn't mind
crawling out from
under my couch and...
Ta-da! Now I'm sitting
over here. Crazy!
By the way,
that rabbit thing?
That was eight
years ago, okay?
I've gotten so much
better since then.
Have you?
Yeah.
Okay, come here.
What is it
that you want?
I wanted to meet you.
Everybody, really.
I want to be a part
of the eye, okay?
I said it. I do.
And I want to use
my magic for good,
like you and merritt
and Jack especially.
Oh, that's right.
I know that Jack is alive.
I know that he
faked his own death.
I am a huge fan
of faking deaths.
That was crazy!
What is this?
A trucker's hitch?
Yeah.
It's terrible.
Embarrassing.
Okay.
By the way,
i am so sorry
that henley left you.
- Ow! God!
- Sorry.
That's actually
a little better.
You know what I heard?
I heard that
she got tired
of waiting around.
She lost faith
and so she asked
for an out,
and the eye
gave it to her.
But who knows, right?
In matters of the heart,
so difficult to tell.
I mean, maybe she got
sick of you.
You ever think
about that?
Maybe you just
didn't tie her up
tight enough. Ow!
Mmm. Here's what's
going to happen.
You're going to stay
here and stop talking,
and I'm going to
make a phone call,
and in about five minutes,
some people are going...
- It's all in the wrist.
Uh-huh.
Let the momentum
of the card
do the work for you.
Mmm-hmm.
This last one
i call the stall.
Not bad.
Now you want to see
a thing of beauty?
I do indeed.
Here you go.
And bingo bango bongo.
No, no, no,
it's good
to be positive
despite making zero
progress in a year.
Yeah.
Whereas when it
comes to hypnotism,
the student has almost
become the master.
I like your confidence,
but you might say that
you have the better teacher.
Ooh!
Yeah.
Your teacher
definitely doesn't know
what he's doing.
By the way, was this
your card yesterday?
In fact it was.
I thought so.
That's not bad.
If I can hypnotize Danny
before you hit him
with a card,
I get top bunk
for a week.
Okay, that's a deal.
Stare at the palm
of your hand and as
your eyes change focus,
you will begin
to notice...
It's not working.
Please don't become him.
I didn't know you guys
did party tricks
when there weren't
floozies around
to impress.
Uh, I think we stopped
trying to impress floozies
in, like, 1937.
Okay, somebody broke
into my apartment,
all right?
Some amateur who knew
everything about me,
everything about
henley leaving,
and everything about us.
That's her.
Hey!
Hi.
You met lula.
I've met her.
What is she doing here?
I'm the new horseman!
I'm the girl horseman.
Whoo!
Yeah!
Nobody.
No excitement.
Jack? Anything?
Dylan, tell me
what's going on here.
Well, lula's been on
the underground scene
for the last decade,
and I think she
has some real talent,
and I'd like to
try her on stage
to balance out the duo.
What?
No, are you serious, man?
After henley left,
you said I could
get back on stage again.
Not someone who
just showed up.
And I really need you
behind the scenes with me
for a little while longer.
Dylan, come on.
I've been behind
the scenes my whole life.
Which is a crime,
might I add. Have you
seen that man's face?
The addition
of some femininity
to the group,
over and above
what atlas provides...
I think the real issue
is we've been in this...
Yeah, the issue
is that we have been
rehearsing for months
for something...
We don't even
know what it is.
And you're going to
keep working until...
Until we work as
a single organism.
I know, I've heard
you say that.
I think what
you're referring to
is us, not you.
Listen, I'm getting
my orders directly
from the eye.
Okay? And then
i give them to you.
Now, if you don't like that,
you're welcome to go.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
But I'm... mmm.
Guys, can i
just weigh in here
really quickly?
Because I think I see
what's going on here.
You guys are this amazing,
tight-knit family unit.
I'm a new person...
We are anything
but a family.
Okay, well, my mother
literally knifed my father
in the neck one time.
So you are actually
a little bit like
my family unit.
Literally?
But, yeah.
It was an accident,
i think.
Okay. So, does this mean
we're actually going
to do something?
Yes.
You've all heard of octa
and their playboy ceo,
Owen case.
His partner, Walter mabry,
died about a year ago.
You wanna know
what all this has
been leading to?
Octa's hosting the launch
of the next-gen cell phone.
Once these phones
hit the streets,
they'll siphon
their users' information
to the black market.
Meaning octa's
selling privacy
to up their profit.
So, the eye has decided
to expose them for it.
Our mission
is to hijack the show.
Rehearsal's over, guys.
This is what we've
been waiting for.
Now it's time
to get to work.
Welcome, octa insiders,
we're delighted that you've
joined us to participate
in our special event.
Today marks the beginning
of a bright new journey
in social networking.
Our latest product,
octa 8...
Keys, cell phones,
iPads, in the bin.
Thank you, sir.
Can't have you texting,
tweeting, recording,
or eating.
Sorry, we will
take very good care
of it for you.
Oh, by the way.
Security memo
from case himself.
Couple of surprise guests.
Just follow his lead, yeah?
We're all good.
I'm heading to
the control room.
All right.
Thanks, Jack.
Atlas, go.
No, Dylan, I can't...
What?
What's the problem?
No, there's
too many people...
Atlas, I got Owen
landing now.
Okay, I'm going now.
Stop.
Oh.
Okay.
Thanks.
Pascal, we need you
in the kitchen.
Look, the speech is
about freedom, okay?
That's what we're
trying to sell here,
is freedom.
Which part of that
do you not understand?
For goodness sake!
I know, I'm sorry.
Mr. case.
Uh, John from legal.
Just need
your signature
for release.
Thank you so much.
Just get it done
and get it back to me.
- Hey there, buddy!
- Smile!
Who are you?
What the hell?
Who am I?
It is picture day.
Did Julie not tell
you it's picture day?
Picture day?
What are you...
Company-wide policy.
Look, I got a job to do.
I have a job to do, too.
Hold on a second.
What is that?
I'm going to need
some backup here.
Who are you calling?
Hey! That's my ID.
Security, my name is
Bo Walsh, thank you.
Hey, I'm Bo Walsh!
Not this guy.
He's not Bo Walsh.
Calm down, please.
Hey! Hey, what's going on?
This guy just came and
put a flashlight in my eyes.
I'm trying to do my job.
This guy, check his badge.
Who is this guy?
I'm Bo Walsh, not him.
It says here,
"Evans mental facility.
"Mark d. Stooge."
Hold on a second.
I've never seen
this before in my life.
Come on, Mr. stooge.
Hold on.
He's not Mr. Walsh!
Come on. Let's go.
What's going on here?
I'm Bo Walsh, not him!
God, you cannot trust
anybody in this city
anymore, can you?
Get off me!
Look, I want to make
a phone call.
I want to call my boss!
Hey, hey! What's going on?
I want to call my boss,
and this jackass...
Hey! Make your phone call.
That's your right, sir.
That's my right.
What the hell?
You're crazy.
Let's go.
This isn't my...
Where's my phone?
Atlas, stooge has left
the building.
The circuit board is ours.
I am leaving backstage.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
- Owen case.
All right.
Lula, show these guys
what you're made of.
I can take over from here.
Clark says you're on break.
What break? Who's Clark?
"Who's Clark?"
That's funny.
Imagine if i
told Roger that,
he'd freak out.
Don't do that!
What?
Who the hell is Roger?
Does Lisa know that
you don't know Roger?
I don't know
who Lisa is.
Are you kidding again?
You don't know
who Lisa is now?
No, I don't. Just get away.
That is
a dangerous...
You're ruining the meat.
Don't make me
have to go to Brian!
I don't know who Brian is!
Why are you
acting like this?
I'll go straight
to him.
Give me that!
Oh, my god!
What are you
doing to me?
- Help me!
- Help her. Go!
Have some water.
I feel from your face
you're freaked
by the flow of blood,
which is fully fixable
in a snap
by focusing and following
the flow of my words
as you're flowing
and floating,
which is why
you're focusing
on my commands.
You got this far in life
by listening to one voice,
the voice in your head.
This is that voice.
Look at the light.
Listen to
your own voice.
Oh, my god.
Wow. What is that?
Is that a miracle towel?
Thank you so much.
Do you know what?
You have taught me
that I'm not cut out
for this kind of work.
I quit!
Get another towel.
Thank you,
and goodbye.
Oh, god.
Welcome everybody!
And now, the moment
that you've all
been waiting for...
Nice work, lady.
Thanks.
Revolutionized music
with octa 2.
I'm actually nervous,
and I'm not even
going onstage.
You know, I've heard
that if you're nervous,
it can be really helpful
to picture each other naked.
It's actually picture
the audience naked.
No, this is new.
This is a new science.
So, I don't know.
Do you want...
We should try it.
Not the right mood.
Guess that leaves
you and me, old buddy.
What? Picture each other...
No. No, thank you.
I mean, I admit,
from the neck up
there are issues.
But from the neck down,
the David.
Owen case.
Good morning,
octa-lites.
Now, I've made the claim
that octa 8 is pure magic.
But the truth is,
that's just one of
those things I say...
That's just one of
...when in fact
i mean something else.
I mean something else.
Well, here to fill
you in on some of my
fabulous lies and hypocrisy,
and to perform some of
the most dazzling feats of
magic you have ever seen...
They are the world's...
...Greatest magicians.
Here to expose me
for the fraud I truly am.
Ladies and gentlemen,
here are the horsemen.
Hello, New York!
Thank you so much.
Hey, it's great to be back.
And have you met
our newest horseman, lula?
- Feels good, right?
- Feels pretty good.
Pretty good.
Thank you, thank you.
Um, okay.
We want to talk to you
about your privacy.
What does your privacy
mean to you?
Because apparently
to Owen case, it means
absolutely nothing.
No, actually
it means less than
absolutely nothing.
You see, he's mocked
your privacy.
Right, and we're not just
talking about the things
that you already agreed to
when you signed,
probably without reading
the terms and conditions
of octas 1 through 7.
Dylan, the FBI is here.
All right.
Don't worry about it.
All right,
go to plan c-4.
Lock the doors.
Hey, boss,
I'm glad you're here.
Don't.
Guys, look.
We got to move around,
get in through the back.
These horsemen
are tricky, okay?
They got backup plans
on top of backup plans.
Hey, sorry,
don't mean to gloat,
but I told you so.
We got an anonymous
phone call an hour ago.
Confirms everything
I've been telling her.
What are you
talking about?
You've been crying wolf
so we wouldn't
send them here.
Boss, please.
Please tell me that you
haven't bought into cowan's
crazy, paranoid fantasia.
We had Owen agree
to a few terms and
conditions of our own.
So, everything
that he had once
considered private...
That he thinks
is really private...
Yeah, everything
that he once considered
private is now...
Oh, my.
As the horsemen
like to say,
magic is about
controlling perception.
You see them
as champions of the truth,
but are they?
Or is that just another
one of their illusions?
- What's going on, rhodes?
- This is crazy.
We got to get everyone
to the other entrance.
Let's go, to the back.
No. You stay here.
So, since they clearly
love secrets...
Let's reveal
some of theirs.
Danny, everyone,
get off the stage.
Abort.
Jack, go with them.
Do you recall the death
of Jack Wilder?
What if I told you
he's not just alive,
but he's actually right here.
And do you know
who else is here?
The FBI.
Let's let them in,
shall we?
And now,
for the big reveal.
Go! Move!
To the stage.
There's a fifth horseman,
and he's the biggest
criminal of them all.
FBI agent, Dylan rhodes.
- I knew it.
- What?
This is so much deeper
than you know, boss.
You think you're
looking at one thing,
but you have no idea.
Who are you?
The same man
I've always been.
Boys, I'm sorry.
You gotta
be kidding me.
- Move! Move!
- Who are those guys?
Who cares? Come on!
- Hurry, hurry!
- Keep going!
How the hell
could this happen?
I thought Dylan had
everything under control.
Yeah.
Apparently he didn't.
Maybe you're
the leak, Dan.
Where you been
sneaking off to?
Don't you dare
for a second
insinuate that I had...
I'm not insinuating.
That's your...
Let's get to the truck,
come on!
- Stay together!
- Move! Move!
Lula, come on!
Coming! Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Sleep. Sleep.
What the hell
is going on?
Wasn't there supposed
to be a truck?
Where the hell are we?
Come on!
Hey, hey! Wait,
did you mis-run the tube?
No, I put it in the truck.
I know I did!
Because we're really
not in the truck right now.
I'm moving! Relax!
There's something
very wrong.
Okay.
Why are we here?
Why am i
frickin' starving?
Yeah,
I'm weirdly starving, too.
This makes no sense.
Okay, sorry.
At least,
and I know this
isn't much consolation,
but apparently
we're now surrounded
by Chinese food.
Right?
I think where we are
right now, they don't refer
to it as "Chinese food."
It's just called
"food."
Wait, what are you saying?
How is this possible?
I believe in your
particular parlance,
the word is
"magic."
That guy looks
exactly like you.
He looks exactly like you.
Are you seeing this
right now?
Chase.
It's like what I heard
about meeting
the rolling stones.
They're a lot
shorter in person.
Remember I told you about
the guy who screwed me
out of everything?
This is
my twin brother, chase.
Wait,
did you do this?
As you can see,
my boss don't mess around.
I do not understand what is
going on right now. At all.
Okay, let me break it
down for you.
You jumped off
a rooftop in New York
and you landed in Macau.
Aka the Vegas of China.
And presto-changeo.
Don't you just love it?
The "greatest magicians
in the world"
are the object
of someone else's
magic trick?
Isn't that poetic?
No?
You know what,
I'm not gonna
let you guys
yuck my yum.
Shoo-shoo. Or mu-shu.
Whatever.
Oh, and you know
what they say,
"what happens in Macau..."
Uh, well, I don't know
the rest of it,
'cause it's
in Chinese, uh...
Hey, thanks, guys!
Reports are coming in
that the infamous horsemen
hijacked the octa
product launch today.
As we learned of
the miraculous resurrection
of Jack Wilder.
And the stunning revelation
that FBI agent Dylan rhodes
has been working as a mole
within the bureau.
Questions abound today
as an international
manhunt is underway
for Dylan rhodes and his
elusive and criminal band
of illusionists.
Hey, seriously,
where are you guys?
I'm at the meetup.
I've been leaving
you messages.
I haven't heard
from anyone.
Please, call me!
Big gains and modest
losses on Thursday.
Hey, tell me you're safe.
Where are you?
- Right where you left me.
- 18 months ago,
agent rhodes.
Thaddeus?
How does it feel
to lose everything?
Your job. Your identity.
Your reason for living.
How does it feel
to be out of control,
perhaps for the first time?
You're a fool, agent rhodes.
You always have been.
Where are they?
I'm not telling
you on the phone!
And if you're wondering
if I was behind
the horsemen's recent debacle,
I'll let you work
that out for yourself.
Hey, I burned you once,
I'll burn you again.
I'm not playing,
Thaddeus.
It's not my game,
agent rhodes. It's yours.
You started it when
you locked me in a cell.
This is simply my move.
Next one is yours.
No!
Let go!
Dad! Help me! Dad!
Dad!
It's all about
blind spots.
When you're staring
straight at something,
and not see it. Why?
Blind spots.
We learned that together.
Didn't we, bro?
Did he tell you that
we were partners once?
No? I didn't think so.
The "mini-mckinneys."
♪ Chasey and a mer-bear
♪ gonna make you scare-bear
♪ ma-ma-magic mckinneys
cool.
And then, one day,
we were 12
and Virginia Von welsheim
had a very nice party
down the street.
I had a little tum-tum,
couldn't go.
Mer-bear did it on his own,
and got a taste
of the solo thing,
and kicked me
to the curb.
Oh, god.
Chase, you win!
I concede.
Delivery guy came to
your door about
a month ago, little za.
Za?
Pizza, huh?
Is this apartment
d3375?
Not even close.
Sleep!
Relaxing, floating,
drifting, dreaming...
Falling.
So, what he did,
my little womb-mate,
is he downloaded all
your private information,
and my employer
had all he needed.
Thanks.
How did you know
how to find him?
That's a very
good question, atlas.
Okay.
Just follow the guards.
They'll take you to my boss.
Been fun playing
this cat-and-mouse
with you, broski.
Meow.
Have fun at the sands.
I am so, so, so sorry.
Don't ever accuse me
of betraying us
again, okay?
Do you guys ever think that
the eye is watching this?
You know, that maybe this
is even what they want?
And at the exact
right moment,
they're gonna swoop in,
and we'll be like,
"yes! Thank god
you're here!
"Thank god! Just in
the Nick of time, eye!"
And then we'll
just celebrate,
and it was all
worth it in the end?
I don't even really
think that, either, so...
It's cool.
Ah.
Ta-da!
So happy to be
working with you.
Please, come in. Come in.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, sorry, how are you
working with us?
Oh, well, as much as
a magician who pulls
a rabbit from a hat
is working
with that rabbit.
We'll be working
together. Yes.
Yeah, you're Walter mabry.
You died a year ago.
Yes. An idea I got
from you, Mr. Wilder.
Fake your death,
the world puts
its guard down.
I'm able to control
quite a few companies,
including my old partner,
Owen's,
as a consortium of so-called
anonymous shareholders.
And that violates
how many sec laws?
I believe it
breaks all of them.
All of them.
You see,
you all want an audience.
Need one, desperately.
It's quite sad, really.
Hence, my ability
to nab you.
I, on the other hand,
want the opposite of that.
I just want to be, and I am
100% off the grid.
You know why?
Yeah, because the grid
is for actual human beings.
No, because in a world
of total surveillance,
the only true freedom
lies in not being seen.
You can't control the grid
from within the grid.
Follow me.
Yeah.
Okay. All right.
You pulled a hat
out of a rabbit.
That was very colorful.
Almost eight and
a half years ago.
So, no need
to bring that up.
We can't all be held
accountable for our
adolescent personas.
Can we, magicolio?
Magicolio,
that was 15 years ago.
Like you, and many others who,
i suppose, were not getting
any sex in high school,
I dabbled with it.
But, uh, unlike you,
i was able to
transition upward
towards actual magic.
Science, you may
have heard it called.
Would you like to know,
my friends,
just how I got you here?
We know how you did it.
No, you don't.
Yeah,
you stole our files
for the show, then
obviously hypnotized us.
The strobe was a combo
of binaural beats,
as well as...
I said stop!
You might not be
having fun, but I am.
You have an unusual
way of showing it.
So...
How did I do it?
You see, magicians
like to control other
people's perceptions.
In your heightened
state of agitation,
you saw the simplest cues.
Black tube, roof.
And your minds
filled in the rest.
But the tube you
meant to go down
was 20 feet to your right.
Go on, sit down.
There's no one
standing in your way.
Don't mind if I do.
Anyway, once in the tube,
yes, you're right...
Blah, blah, blah,
the strobe contained
uv letters pulsing
the word "sleep."
And that, combined with
the sound, put you into
an instant Alpha pattern.
Sleep, sleep, sleep.
And from then on,
it really was just fun.
And I can assure you,
you don't know
what happened.
That's really creepy.
Really, really creepy.
That's not cool.
Yep, easy stuff, magic,
if you put your mind to it.
All right, that's enough.
So why are we here, then?
Besides you getting
to show off how
adorably clever you are.
Well, to start with,
the man you stole from
last year,
turns out I had invested
quite a lot of money
in some of his companies,
so a lot of what you
stole was, in fact, mine.
Good news is,
it's very easy for you
to pay me back.
I just need your skills.
Owen and I were
like the Beatles,
if the Beatles had been...
Elfin?
...geniuses.
Pretty sure the Beatles
were geniuses.
And like them,
we had a dream.
Could we create actual,
genuine magic?
And I'm guessing one of you
achieved that dream,
and it wasn't you?
That is what he
would like you to think.
Was a perfect blend
of elegance and technology.
But Owen
wanted it for himself
so he humiliated me
by exposing my private files
to the board of directors
and convinced them
that I am unstable.
Did you take
a picture of him
while he was sleeping?
He had me kicked out of
my own company,
taking credit for a chip
that's not just
the key to one computer,
but every computer
system on the planet.
It can un-encrypt anything,
crack the defense firewall,
manipulate markets,
and spy on anyone.
And now it's being sold
to the highest bidder.
If you're so rich,
why don't you just buy it?
So he gets the money?
And the pleasure? No.
Why would I buy it
when I could have you
steal it for me?
It's being previewed tomorrow
to the various suitors,
which will
include your targets,
a crew lead by
a south African gangster.
Yes. How your team
gets past security,
that's up to you.
But once you do, you just need
to inspect it and steal it.
Come on, this is
perfect for you, isn't it?
You're magicians and thieves.
What makes you think
we would even
consider doing this?
Um, oh, wait, I had a reason.
What was it? Oh, yes.
You see, back home,
you're wanted criminals.
But here,
i control the police,
the casinos, the media.
I can give you a new life,
out of hiding.
And if you don't,
I'll have you killed.
You know what?
I'm not stealing
a thing for you.
Not unless Dylan
tells me it's okay.
Really?
Dylan is where,
exactly?
Yeah, I'm with him.
So you can go
ahead and kill us
because I'm not
gonna steal anything
for you either.
Strikes me
that a consensus seems
to be forming, Walter,
and we're calling
your bluff.
Actually,
we'll do it.
What?
We're in Macau.
The oldest magic store
in the world is here.
We'll get
the supplies we need,
and we'll do it.
Thank you.
Chase will take you
to the magic shop
in the morning.
Badge.
Really?
Thanks.
Agent cowan.
Your ID.
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
It appears Mr. Bradley's
still at dinner.
Yeah? Tell him
recess is over.
What?
Where are they?
I don't have time
for bullshit.
Oh, I have all the time
in the world, thanks to you.
And I didn't get to
finish my lobster,
which makes me very grumpy.
Okay, let's cut the crap.
What do you want?
You can dispense
with the tough guy act
to begin with.
You're too desperate
for it to be believable.
I said,
what do you want?
You used
a form 219 warrant
you found a connection
between me
and the four horsemen.
Which means
you can take me
out of here
on a 24-hour leave.
You want me
to break you out?
I want you
to take me out.
All you need is
an extradition order,
which you'll find in
that tray by my printer.
I had nothing to do
with the horsemen's
disappearance.
You were lured
into a trap.
And like Dorothy did
when she landed in oz,
you're beginning
to realize
that the only way out
is through.
And I'm the only one
who can get you there.
You got this place wired.
You don't need me
to get out of here.
This is all about payback.
I believe in
an eye for an eye.
So you're out
to destroy me?
You think I'm still gonna
play your little game?
I know you will.
Because no matter
how hard you try
to find a culprit
behind all this,
you're going to blame
only yourself.
When your little vendetta
ended with you putting me
in jail 18 months ago,
you got tired,
you got sloppy. You
stopped paying attention.
And that's where you lost.
So,
you can save yourself,
or you can make
a deal with me,
and save the four horsemen,
and stop wasting
both of our time.
Steal something
for this narcissistic
little man boy?
I don't like it.
But what I like less
is you deciding for us.
Yeah? Do you like that
we're the laughing stocks
of the magic world,
and the fugitives
of the actual world?
Walter is right.
We have nowhere to go.
But we can fix that.
We can fix it?
Yeah.
So you're officially
part of the team now?
Excuse me?
I'm sure this
is what Dylan
meant when he said
we should all work
as a single organism.
Yeah, that is a fairytale
that Dylan tells himself,
and tells us.
Look, even if
we get this stick,
he'll never let us go.
We can't trust Walter, okay?
The eye has
a history in Macau.
They're the only
ones we can trust.
Now, if we can
get it to them,
they can clear our names
and get us
the hell out of here.
It's a bad plan, man.
Hey.
Hi, how are you?
Um, we need some
things custom-made.
Actually, by tomorrow.
We're kind of in a rush.
And...
You have no idea what
I'm talking about, do you?
Welcome to iong's.
My name's li. Not Bruce Lee.
What?
Got you.
Okay.
Look.
Oh! And now it's
by my head. How fun.
$20.
$20?
No, thank you.
We're kind of in a rush.
$10.
Uh, no.
Okay, all right.
Just give us
the thumbs. Yeah?
Okay. Thanks a lot,
Jack. Please take these.
So, we need
a keplinger holdout,
and we also need
roughing fluid,
a sanada gimmick,
sleeves, tracks.
This is all in plastic,
though, if you can.
What?
My grandmother
wants to know why plastic?
Plastic is cheap.
Sorry. Yeah, we need plastic
because we're...
We're going through
a very sensitive
metal detector, okay?
So plastic, nothing.
Metal...
It detects.
What did she say?
She said just because
you're talking slowly
and moving your hands
doesn't mean
she can suddenly
understand English.
Oh, yeah.
So sorry. He's racist.
Listen, I know that
the only thing
that we agree on
is that our mom and dad
had one too many children.
So why don't we just let
the kids play with their toys
and go get
a little drinkey-poo?
If it's free, it's me.
Great.
Guys, we'll be right back.
Okay, kiddies,
the chaperones
are watching you.
Don't do anything
i wouldn't enjoy.
Okay.
Have fun, you two.
Hey.
Can I use your phone?
It's kind of important.
Sure.
On the house.
Thanks.
I'm arranging
to hand over the stick.
So that's how we've been
contacting the eye?
You've been doing it
on your own?
Maybe.
Oh, god.
Dylan's not
gonna like this.
I'm not really concerned
with what Dylan likes.
Okay?
I'm doing this for us.
What is wrong
with this thing?
Hey, relax,
it's just a kid's toy.
Yeah, that's
what I thought.
Okay. Let me just...
Ow!
Sorry, sorry. Jesus.
Hey, can you get this?
It's like birth,
you know.
One person
enters the hospital,
two people come out.
Walk and talk.
I'll tell you
on the plane.
What plane?
My sources tell me
your horsemen
are in Macau.
What's the look?
It's none of your business.
Who are your sources?
Just some old friends.
When we have the card,
where do I go?
And 0 for 52.
Well, it's perfect.
It's a perfect score.
Then what about girls?
Like, relationships?
What?
Look, it's not
something I'm proud of,
but every girl
i get close to,
I end up
taking their trust.
And then their wallet.
So...
You take their wallets?
Yeah.
You ever take
their belts?
Or how about
some peanuts
from the hotel bar?
Not sure why
you took those.
I'm sorry, did you think
that I was like
those other girls?
Oh, Jack.
Okay. So there's
a marketplace
down the street.
And I'm meeting
a man with a blue hat.
He'll get the stick
to the right people
and get us home.
You go grab merritt, okay?
We got a lot to do.
And, hey,
put your belt on.
Oh, no, it's not...
She took it off me and...
You know,
the most heartbreaking
moment of my life
was when I discovered
that you had stolen
all my money and split.
I didn't realize until now
how much of that money
you put into your face.
Seriously, is it weird
to have more hair in your
nose than on your head?
Speaking of, next time
you get a hair transplant,
you might wanna
consider requesting
something other
than old man pubes.
You know what?
You are such a buffoon,
mer-bear.
And this little ploy
you have
of stalling me
while your friends
screw over my employer?
Not gonna work.
Chase!
As you stare
into my eyes,
you will find
that you wanna sleep.
When you wake, you will beg
for merritt's forgiveness
and realize that
you will never be
half the man that he is.
Merritt,
I am so, so
very, very sorry
about how pathetic
your pupil is.
Hey, a little hint
on your technique
of surprise.
It lacks that all-essential
little element of surprise.
Hey, this has been fun,
mer-bear.
Let's do it again
sometime.
Well,
I've had ample time to do
some research, and you know,
I think the eye
might actually be real.
Thought you didn't
buy into all that.
I'd be lying if i
said I didn't think
that this road would lead
to the great wizard
behind the curtain
and, in the end,
i might get to see his face.
Even if the fate of
the horsemen depends on it?
Listen to me.
I broke you out of there.
We're not
changing the terms now.
You put me there!
Yeah,
because you deserve
to be there.
Listen, I did not
kill your father.
All right, all right,
let's just cut the bullshit.
I know who you are,
shrike.
I know you blame me
for your father's death.
I know you think
i goaded him into performing
a trick he couldn't pull off.
I know the time in
jail was a result
of a 30-year revenge plot
against me.
Supposing that's all true,
you think I'd tell you now?
Man.
30 years.
And the greatest long game
magic trick ever created.
Just to put me
behind bars.
Okay.
So how did it feel,
seeing me there?
Was it all you hoped?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You're lying.
It was an empty experience.
And you wanna know
how I know?
I know because you know.
There's always, always more
than what's on the surface.
So what,
the past didn't happen,
and you're not
who I think you are?
Now, don't tell me
in 30 years
that's the first time you've
asked yourself that question.
I am not my father.
You're not getting
in my head, okay?
You think you're
luring me into a trap?
You're not.
Now, I am desperate,
which means I'm dangerous.
My only concern is
the health and well-being
of the horsemen.
And you're gonna
lead me to them.
And if you don't,
I promise you,
you're gonna end up
far worse
than in some cushy
jail cell somewhere.
What if the horsemen
don't actually
need you to save them?
All right.
So the lab is made up
of two distinct layers,
the security perimeter
and the clean room.
The stick we're looking for
should be in this core.
So we're gonna have to
get underneath, extract it,
and replace it with a decoy.
Luckily, it's similar
in weight and size
to a playing card,
so we're gonna have to
brush up on our card-istry.
Whoa, whoa!
That's no good.
So how do we get in?
Hannes pike.
He's the son of
a south African gangster.
He's rsvp'd with
what looks like
a couple of members
of his security detail.
A doctor, to vet it, I guess,
and somebody named Buffy.
Yeah, apparently,
he travels with a different
bimbo every week. Hmm.
I wonder which one of us
gets to play the bimbo.
Hey, can I get in?
At the soothing
sound of the slots
you slip into a serene state
of slumber and sleep.
They will think you're hannes,
so lead them out
and keep them busy.
You trust your
people implicitly.
You will have them
take care of everything,
and you will wait
in the car.
And eyes open,
wide awake. Go.
Excuse me.
These people
are following me.
You might wanna
check their pockets.
Then our time is
ticking to infiltrate the lab
and get the card
to the market,
where I'll hand it off
to the eye,
so we can all
get the hell home.
Ah! Hannes, my old friend.
So glad
you could make it.
I knew you had
a soft spot for
an old-school bidding war.
How have you been?
I trust my people
implicitly.
Certainly. But I'm sure
you'd like to see
it for yourself.
Hold it in your hands,
check the build quality.
Or not. Also fine.
Well, if you'd like
to follow me.
You'll have to
remove all your metal.
Watches, rings, etc.
Yeah, of course.
Excuse me for asking...
Where might i
have seen you before?
I don't know, probably
one of my many symposiums.
The book jacket!
I have to say,
Dr. michaelakis,
I'm a huge fan.
Oh,
thank you so much.
Uh, which book?
There have been so many.
Does hannes' chippy
always talk for you, doctor?
Doctor?
Sorry, when you say "chippy,"
you are referring
to Buffy here, yeah?
Of course.
Hannes prefers
the term "floozy"
for all his boy toys.
Yeah. He does.
That's good.
Noted.
By the way,
i got your email,
Dr. michaelakis.
You had a query
about our ability
to maintain quantum coherence
at room temperature
without the use of dilution,
refrigerators,
or error correction.
Do you care
to elucidate?
Right.
Yeah.
Yes, I did send that email.
The other day, I saw you.
I did, I sent it.
So what gives?
I'm sorry, what gives...
I think what
she's trying to say...
Actually, the grown-ups
are having a meeting, Buffy.
Okay.
If you'll hold on to that.
Yeah, sure, doctor.
Thank you.
Now, every seventh grader,
even the dumb ones,
know the second law
of thermodynamics.
"All ordered systems
tend toward disorder."
Disorder!
So I'm going to ask you one
more time, sir, what gives?
Well, it's actually
topological quantum order.
The emergence of
quantum effects
on a macroscopic level.
So that is,
in fact, what gives.
Thank you.
You know,
Buffy is not a bad
name for you.
You know,
buff, firm, taut.
That's good.
Did you just find
a thesaurus somewhere?
Nubile.
- That's good.
- Thank you. Okay.
There we go.
Sorry, sorry.
The stick's metal.
How are we going
to get it out?
Yeah. I don't know.
This is the housing.
820 million qubit miles
of digi-synaptic resonance.
But of course, what sets us
apart from anything
else on the planet
is the processor,
which we playfully refer to
as the magic broomstick.
The broomstick?
Has the power to
clear the contents
of any computing
system on the planet
and then magically
sweep them into your bin.
Ah! Broomstick.
That's funny.
Take a look,
vet it however you'd like,
and tell hannes we'll be
taking bids on Monday.
Thank you.
Oh, my god.
I must be allergic
to something in here.
What could you possibly be
allergic to in here?
This room is
hermetically sealed.
That's it.
If we could get him away
from the computer, please.
That's the one thing.
Just until
he's recovered.
We're gonna need
some anti-bacterial...
Do we have
alcohol wipes?
Your hands need to be
sterile if you intend
to get any closer.
Do I make myself clear?
Sorry. We couldn't...
No, I'm fine.
...take his medicine
into the country.
Yeah.
Can't risk
any contamination.
You're gonna have to stay away
from the inner workings.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
All right.
If you're done...
Oh. Here you go.
Sorry about this.
Okay. I'm okay.
This happens to him
sometimes. It'll pass.
Allergies.
Nothing you can do.
Well, something
you could do, doctor.
Okay?
Search him, please.
Didn't we
just do that?
Okay. I wanna run
full diagnostics
on the system.
This is completely
unnecessary.
Up, up.
Okay.
Ah!
Hey! I can walk on my own.
Whoa!
Sorry.
Hey!
I can do that myself.
We just met, man.
Handsy, handsy, handsy.
Hey!
My eyes are up here, man.
How do you like it?
Hey, I'm good.
Turn around.
Do you have anything?
I don't know.
Can't trust anybody.
I'm good.
They're clean.
Do your final checks
and get them out of here.
Oh, we're walking
this way again. Yay.
I don't speak
the language.
See?
What did I tell you, man?
We didn't have anything.
Thanks, pal. Appreciate that.
Something about
a big white dance floor,
makes me wanna boogie.
Hey, thanks for having us.
That's great stuff.
You guys are pretty serious
about your security, huh?
Okay.
Do I have all my things?
I feel like I came in
with more stuff.
Did I come in
with more stuff?
You don't think so?
Uh, sir, I think you
still have my wallet.
Remember, I, uh, gave it
to you when I came in?
It would be nice
to leave with it.
Wallet coming through.
Sorry, my belt.
Uh...
I guess that's
everything, right?
Thank you.
That is not a toy,
Buffy.
Sorry.
Go, go, go!
All right. Now,
drop me off at the market
you asked me to call you when
they started running around
like headless chickens.
Well, that's
what's happening.
This is where your sources
told you they'd be?
No, this is where
my sources said
we might find an answer.
She must be familiar
with your work.
Excuse me.
Miss, have you seen
these people?
She says her grandson
spoke to their leader.
He's in the back.
What?
No "wow,
you speak mandarin"?
Ah! The coffin
to the beyond.
It was always a flap,
or a trap or mirrors.
The audience thought
he'd just disappeared.
But he was always
hidden somewhere inside.
I believe that's
the prototype for the one
your father had made.
He, like many others
over the years,
ordered his supplies
from here.
Ah!
Of course.
That's why
you gave me the look
when I said
they were in Macau.
Your father
used to come here
when you were young.
Can I please get
some space here?
You think you're
the only one who'd
wondered for 30 years
what happened?
You're not.
Lionel was
a master magician.
Either he gamed the hinges,
so he could kick the door
and they would pop out,
or he had access
to the lock
from the inside
so he could pick it.
Word is
the safe was made
from cheap metal,
and it bowed.
Still, he always had
something up his sleeve.
Unless he'd
reached the limit
of his capabilities
and his clock ran out.
Excuse me.
My grandmother
has something
you might want.
This was your father's.
He had several
of these made.
And the horsemen?
I overheard
them talking.
One of them, atlas,
he's meeting someone
at the market nearby.
As for
former agent rhodes,
his location is now
your number one priority.
We're putting out
an international apb.
Including cooperation
from local authorities.
Agent cowan.
I'm assuming it was
actually not you
who walked into
newburgh federal prison,
then walked out
30 minutes later
with Thaddeus Bradley?
What?
He used your ID.
What are you doing,
rhodes?
Atlas, hey.
Dylan.
I blew it, I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help now.
Okay, we definitely
don't need your help.
I know I messed up,
all right?
Yeah, you put everybody's
lives in danger.
Where is everybody?
I can't be seen
with you actually,
right now.
I got it now, okay?
I appreciate you taking
the time to take control
for a little while.
Hey, I'm actually...
Yeah?
Yeah, but I got it now,
all right? Yeah.
You do?
You look like you can
get some rest, buddy.
Who you meeting here?
I'm not meeting anybody.
They told me at iong's
you were meeting somebody.
At iong's?
Okay, yeah,
no, I am, um...
I'm meeting somebody
from the eye.
To exchange
this computer chip
for our lives back.
I hope you're happy
with the situation
you've put us in.
You're talking
to the eye?
Yeah.
Why are you talking
to the eye?
Atlas.
Atlas,
give me the stick.
Dylan, you're not our
leader anymore, okay?
You're not our hero.
You're not FBI.
You're not
a magician.
really anything.
And we trusted you
for a year.
So if you really
wanna help us...
If you really
wanna help us,
you would leave.
I get it. Cool.
Bye.
Yeah, that was me you called
at the magic shop.
So much fun though,
knowing you'd
be scurrying away
from me at the lab
just to bring it
to me here.
Did you actually
think I'd let you go?
How did you do that?
Everyone has their button.
You push it
and they go blind.
And yours,
obviously, is ego.
"Stay the course.
"Great changes
are in store.
"Trust that
your unique talents
"will not go
unrecognized."
That was you.
Yeah.
Merritt downloaded
all the files,
but how do you think
we were able to find him?
I asked to see the face
behind all of this.
What you actually
put your phone on
was a bi-wave siphon pad.
Once again,
science beats magic.
So, the stick?
No.
I got it!
I got it. I got it.
Fuck, Dylan!
Wait, leave them!
You really think
I'm gonna walk away
from you?
Give me the stick!
All right. Don't ever
question me again.
Beat it!
So, the stick.
Go to hell.
Boys.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
There's like 10 of you.
Come on,
he's just doing tricks.
He's there!
Go!
Oh...
Dylan, watch
the pretty birdies fly.
And sleep.
Doesn't work on me.
Not even
as a distraction?
Good job.
Nice to be involved.
Hey, guys! Guys! Hey!
I just saw Dylan.
Um, something happened.
What do you mean
you just saw Dylan?
Dylan's here?
What happened?
- Atlas.
- I don't know.
What are they doing?
Those are Walter's men.
This is what they want.
What the hell?
How do you
still have that?
Whoa. That's
Lionel shrike's safe.
What the hell
do they want with that?
Okay, we gotta
follow that truck.
They must have Dylan.
We don't have much time.
What do you want?
You to understand something
very important.
We
are mirror images.
I share
a very deep connection
with my father.
And like you,
I'll stop at nothing
to avenge any wrongs
done to him.
You know the only difference
between your father and mine?
Mine's still alive.
Get him up.
So,
this is the man
who spent a lifetime
plotting against me.
I wouldn't have
known your face
if it had been on a billboard
outside my bedroom window.
But you have spent,
what, 30 years
thinking about mine?
When my father died,
your insurance company
denied my mother her claims.
I wouldn't
even have known...
She died a pauper!
...who your mother was.
She was a digit,
a nanobyte
in a stream of data.
Because nothing
is personal to you
and everyone and everything
is just a number,
isn't that so?
That is where
you are wrong,
Mr. rhodes.
Once you made yourself known
it became very personal.
My son...
Yeah, the sociopath.
Funny thing is,
I have seven so-called
legitimate children.
Sniveling, snobbish,
stupid runts.
I have one illegitimate child
who is a lot like me.
The point is,
he wants something,
and like any good parent,
I will stop at nothing
to get it for him.
Your horsemen have it.
You will turn it and them
over to us, now.
No.
Dylan, I would
like you to really
take this moment
because this is
the consequence
of your personal
vendetta come to life
and staring you
in the face.
I want you to know
that when you're gone,
we're gonna destroy
everything you believe in,
starting with the horsemen,
and ending with the eye.
Now then,
cast your mind back
to standing by
the banks of the river
watching your father descend,
disgraced and discredited.
The horrid psychic pain
as you have relived for years.
I felt that same thing
as you drained not
just my father's fortune,
but his dignity!
And yet you took
pleasure from it.
This should bring back
some childhood memories.
Would you like
some tea?
Oh. Thank you.
You ready?
Over to you.
Splash!
Job done!
Hell is going
to seem like
a day at the spa
by the time we're through
with these horsemen.
- Wouldn't you say?
- You had me at "hell."
I love you so much.
Always keep something
up my sleeve.
I wish I could dredge
from the muck of my soul
one speck of remorse,
but I can't.
So I'll stick to
the business at hand
and try not to smile
too broadly.
And, uh, thank you
for delivering
Mr. Dylan rhodes.
I take it it's done.
Literally hit
the bottom.
Now,
where are the horsemen?
They're performers.
Their pride, their ego...
Their need to be adored
are all too powerful
to keep them out of
the limelight for long.
If they don't make
themselves known,
you will find yourself
in a very similar position
to Mr. rhodes.
Are we clear about that?
As clear as the water
he's under.
You'll have the rest
when I have the horsemen.
Dylan!
Dylan, come on,
buddy, breathe!
- Dylan.
- Dylan?
Dylan, come on!
You're okay.
Jesus! You scared
the hell out of us, man.
Are you all right, bro?
Okay!
Thank you!
This is the least
i could do.
No. There's a hell of a lot
less you could've done.
That was not an option.
You took a bullet
for us, it was huge.
You really did, man.
Thanks for
pulling me out.
Seriously.
Yeah.
You got yourself out.
We did the easy part.
Literally, in my case,
I was just standing
on the shore while
atlas jumped down
and got you.
I'm serious.
Hey, you guys.
Something's not right.
- What's wrong?
- What?
It's fake.
What?
No, I had the stick.
The actual stick.
I swear, it was in my hand.
In the lab.
And then I put it in
the little case thing.
And I gave it to atlas.
Is there any
chance you've possibly
misplaced it at any point?
I took it from you
and then slipped it
back in your coat
when I pushed you out.
Either way, we're
left holding a whole
sack full of nada.
Yeah, but they're gonna
come after us as if
we do have something.
No. Okay.
I agree that somebody
got the better of us.
But I don't agree
that we have a sack
full of nada.
Because we're all here.
That's a sack
full of something.
We all know that Walter
is not going to stop
until he gets that chip.
And we're the only ones that
even know that he's alive.
We can't just walk away.
That's not what
the horsemen do.
There's a quote. Um...
It's actually
by the magician
that made me wanna do this
in the first place.
It's, uh...
"A magician's greatest power
lies forever shrouded
"in his empty fist."
"And the very idea
that he can convince
the world
"that he is, in fact,
carrying with him a secret."
That's Lionel shrike.
Right.
That we should pretend like
we have something we don't?
What is Walter's
greatest fear?
Being seen.
And what does
the stick do?
The stick can
unencode anything.
It can open up a back door
into any computer
on the planet.
Including his.
Yeah.
Right, we not only make him
think that we have it,
but that we're going to use it
to expose and destroy him.
We need a plan.
But we don't have time.
We have each other and
there are five of us.
But we also
need supplies, right?
And resources.
And probably more
than five people.
Do you really think
you don't have help?
Oh, she speaks English.
Of course. Yeah.
Do you know why
the fool is the most
powerful card in the tarot?
Not because the person
who draws him is a fool.
He's a fool
because he's a clean slate,
and, therefore, can become
anything.
You were chosen.
All of you.
Not because of
who you are,
but because of who
you might become.
When you say "chosen"...
Are you part of
the eye?
Yes.
We are part of
the eye.
You've each
doubted our existence.
Wondering
if we, indeed,
were watching.
We are.
We always have been.
This is the best
magic shop in the world.
You know what
she's saying, right?
Yes.
That now we have
resources and help.
Thank you.
So, who's in?
I'm in.
Yeah, I'm in.
Let's do this.
No, no, no.
Not long ago,
we were tricked.
I was exposed
and brought back
from the dead.
So we thought
it was only fitting
that we do the same thing
to the person
who did it to us.
Midnight, new year's Eve.
London.
We will be performing
a series of shows
that all connect
to our big finale,
so pay close attention
to each trick.
Get my father.
I want interpol,
Scotland yard,
whoever we have in London.
What do we know
about rhodes?
Wherever the horsemen are,
that's where he is.
Because we, too, will bring
someone back from the dead.
Let's move, everyone!
In front of
the largest stage
in the world...
The actual world.
You know they're
playing you, right?
Leading you into a trap?
Yeah, but the threat
is real.
This card can hack into
any system on the planet,
including ours.
They have it, why wouldn't
they use it to expose us?
Me. Everything we've done.
Is it real,
Mr. mckinney?
The threat is real.
So, how do we stay
ahead of them?
We need to get
to London by midnight.
On this new year's Eve, and
the crowds are out in force.
Locals and tourists alike
getting ready for
the party of the year.
A video gone viral
from the infamous
horsemen magicians
has surfaced.
But will
it end in their arrest
on national television?
Or some sort of vindication?
But we do
know, wherever, whenever that
is, people will be watching.
Yeah, texts, tweets,
instagrams.
Anything that says
"horsemen," brags about
seeing the horsemen,
tag them and bundle them.
Dad, who do we have
security-wise on this?
Your guys?
Well, we want all of them
and all their friends.
Stationed throughout the city,
so they can be anywhere
in 60 seconds.
Hello! Hey!
My name's Jack Wilder.
Goddamn,
it feels good
to be back.
All right,
gather around.
I wanna talk to you about
something real quick.
You all know three card monte,
also known as "find the lady"?
Trick performed by street
hustlers all over the world.
And why street hustlers?
Because as soon as you walk up
to the table, you lose.
Every time.
Let me demonstrate.
While we're at it,
let's find ourselves
a life-sized queen.
Ma'am, would you
mind being my queen?
Don't worry.
I promise you
there's a 50% chance
you'll get her back
after the show.
Head over there.
Thank you very much.
All right. Let's find
ourselves some Jacks
to serve our queen!
Trust me, gentlemen.
I know how
these guys work now.
They're gonna start
with a tease.
A few little pop-ups.
Something to
lure you in. Like...
Well, you know...
Like three card monte,
where the guy goes,
"looky here,
but no, no, looky here!"
Except when all these
little tricks are done,
the only thing
you're gonna be looking at
is the inside of your own
colon, with the words
"horsemen"
written all over it.
In blood.
We get the picture,
Mr. mckinney.
And get out
of my chair.
Hello, everybody!
Come close, come on!
All right,
all right, so listen.
Tonight, I am going
to make something fly
using actual magic.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah!
I'm going to take
a very large vessel,
I'm gonna make
it fly over there
and land on the thames.
Can you handle that?
Same rules
apply as before.
All you need to do is
keep your eye on the queen.
It's as simple as that.
- Are you guys ready?
- Yeah!
Dad, look at this.
Near the river. Looks like
the shows are starting.
But we're not the only ones
who found them.
What do you mean?
It's on channel one.
- Let's go to 2.
- Here we go.
Got him.
We have a location.
It's Jack Wilder.
Here come the horsemen.
Okay, we're moving.
Let's go, let's go.
Turn around.
Hide yourselves
with the cards.
And here we go.
You guys still
have your eye on her?
You want me to
go back and do it?
Okay, all right.
I'm moving on.
And switch.
Where is she?
Down at the end?
You sure?
All right,
can I get a drumroll
from my man in the back?
Thank you very much.
Uh-oh.
There's my girl.
Not my girl.
100% your girl.
But just
in this situation.
Okay, but I gotta warm up
a little bit first. Okay?
So, uh, let me just
make something small
fly, like...
Fly, fly, fly!
Wow, right?
Look at that!
Aw. Come on, people.
Tough crowd. You, fly!
Me?
Check your fly.
You like that?
You support
that relationship?
That guy had
a bird in his pants.
That's disgusting.
Copy that. We've got
two sightings reported.
Heading to greenwich market.
Get me Thaddeus.
Thaddeus, the FBI are here.
They're moving.
Let 'em move.
Well, what if they
get there first?
That can't happen.
I guarantee you, they won't.
Find the pattern.
You do that,
and you'll be able
to cut them off
before they get to
their final trick.
If it makes you feel better,
I'll take care of the FBI.
I guess you found me!
We've got a third spot.
Okay, everybody,
we're getting a pattern.
Um... give me 2,
13 and 21.
What the hell is that?
Freeze that and zoom in.
How the hell
did this happen?
He's dead.
We watched him drown.
How the hell did this happen?
Given that it did happen,
the pertinent question is,
what are we
gonna do about it?
We're gonna stop him, dad.
We'll stop him.
Where's my coat?
Walter, for the record,
i never loved the safe idea.
Oh, I know
where they're going.
The next show is merritt's
and it's by the river.
So we can find the horsemen's
entry point for the finale.
I've a confession to make.
I've been told I have
some control issues.
I've learned that it's really,
really hard to control people,
so I'm gonna try
to control something
that's a lot
easier than people.
I'm gonna try to
control the weather.
Yeah, rain, um...
It'd be a little difficult
to make it rain, right?
That would be something
that only god can do, right?
I'm gonna do something
that god can't do.
I'm not just gonna
make it clear up.
No, no, no.
I'm gonna make
it actually stop.
And can god do that?
Mmm. No, I don't think so.
Or what about make it go up?
Are you still with me?
Watch the queen on the left.
Let's do it.
Turn around.
Switch!
Show me the lady.
Show me the lady!
The end? End?
You know what?
I'm actually starting
to feel kinda bad.
It's just because
i can actually feel
that you guys are
paying attention.
You know, it's unfortunate
that it's the wrong
kind of attention.
Yeah, we need a fresher bird.
He's so cute. He's so cute!
Let's kill him, right?
Merritt,
move into position.
Got it, Dylan.
Uh, I'm on my way.
I'll see you there.
Lula, stand by, all right?
Or, what about just go,
i don't know, just go insane?
Reports are coming in
from all over London
as the horsemen
appear to have taken over
the whole city for their show.
Hey, broski-whaddya-knowski?
Where you headed?
Please, bro, don't do this.
Where are you headed?
North, south, east?
East. Tower of London?
Tower bridge?
Near tower bridge?
The thames!
You're going to
the thamesy-whemsy!
You're so easy!
Bro,
if there's any chance of us
ever having a relationship...
There's not.
Where's your entry?
South bank? Greenwich?
Greenwich.
I know where
you're going. I know where...
Watch it, hobo.
Hey, merritt. Oh, come on.
Tell me you're kidding. How?
When?
Shit. All right.
All right, I got it.
Don't worry about it.
I'll warn the others.
Sorry. Just...
What? I just told you...
Phone call.
- Hello?
- Lula.
Dylan. Ah, yeah.
Kind of in the middle
of something right now.
Wrap it up.
Meet me at
the rendezvous point now.
What?
Now!
Was that an act of god?
No. No, no, no,
that was an act of me
and the strobe lights
and rain machines.
And I hope you guys
were paying attention.
Because you're
gonna need to know
all of that for the final.
So how did I do it?
Did I use a Barry trap?
Maybe some switches
or a few duplicates?
Jack, go now!
You know what?
I hate to say it.
You're gonna have
to wait to find out.
I know.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I love you all.
Lula, go!
I have to go.
Out of the way, FBI!
Move, move, move! Go!
Get some men in that park!
You gonna
fill up on appetizers?
Or save room for
the main course?
Where the hell
are the horsemen?
You're just gonna wind up
holding your own tails.
Or, you can let them
come to you.
So, what's it gonna be?
Chase them?
Or make a deal with me?
Again? How did we
get found out again?
It's fine, it's fine.
We'll just cut to the finale.
Where's merritt?
Fine. I don't know.
I'm here.
Where's lula?
I'm right here!
What the hell happened?
My goddamn brother happened.
Don't worry about it.
We just gotta get
to the destination.
Lula, can you
handle that thing?
I can ride it.
Have you asked the guys
that question, or just me?
Yeah, good point.
Let's go!
No, Jack.
Shit!
Jack's down.
We gotta get him.
Come on, move!
- Jack! Go, go!
- That's the brake.
That's the gas.
You'll figure it out.
Come on, follow me!
That's it?
Ahh!
Hey, ready?
Yeah!
Get on.
Okay, guys, I'm coming!
Whoa!
Jesus!
I'm coming!
Get up! Come on!
Okay.
You got me.
Those things are
really dangerous!
- Come on!
- Go!
Get him in! Move it!
What is happening?
Where are they?
They should be
arriving any second.
That is, if they're gonna
get here by midnight.
Ah!
Okay, feeling fear.
Fear.
Anger, anger.
Oh, full house!
That's enough.
I was done.
So nice to see you all again.
But since we're
such old friends,
let's skip the formalities.
One of you
has something we require.
So give it over.
Nothing at all?
Really?
Sit down!
Let's go, let's go!
Hurry up and move them quickly
before they can do anything.
Get those lights off me!
Get on the plane!
Ow! Hey!
Hey!
Whoa, whoa, hey!
Yeah, uh,
take off immediately.
You know, you make it
almost too easy?
I mean,
even your hilarious attempts
to make
yourselves unpredictable,
just follow
the same pattern
each time.
Set up, set up, set up.
Which tonight was going
to be stroke of midnight,
middle of the thames?
Tell me if I'm warm.
Well, there will be
a big reveal, and
it will come now.
The stick, dear boy.
- No.
- Fine.
Start with her.
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey, hey!
Give it to him.
Danny, give him the card.
- Just give it to him.
- Danny, come on.
We'll have a closer look.
Okay, I owe you an apology.
Leader, you should have
planned an escape, okay?
This is the both of us.
Okay, it's the both of us.
Guys, come on!
Come on, stop!
You, to save your
little girlfriend!
To save my...
He had a knife
to her head!
I'm a horseman, you dick!
All right, you know what?
This is not the time!
And you,
what's your deal, man?
Look, they're not
gonna get blood
they're probably gonna
throw us out of the plane.
Really?
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I just have to
say congratulations.
And thank you!
It's real.
What?
It's real?
Bring them through.
Did you say it's real?
What is
he talking about?
Move!
Well done, my boy.
Cote du marisule champagne.
It's the most
expensive bottle
on earth.
$1.2 million.
And I saved it just
for this occasion.
Honestly, same bottle,
liquor shack, 700k.
Hey.
You got what you wanted.
So, does this mean
you're letting us go?
Knowing what you
know about us? No.
You sure?
Chase, what shall we do?
Toss them out.
Get your last words
in quickly, everybody!
No! Come on! No!
Farewell.
Oh, god! No!
Wait! I just wanna say.
I came into the world
with the wrong family,
but I'm leaving
with the right one.
I love you guys!
No!
No, no, no!
This is how I kicked
you out of the womb.
No!
Who's next?
No, wait! Let me go!
Let go of me!
No, no, no!
Let me go!
Toss her!
Oh, god!
Hurry up and
shut that door!
It's getting
cold in here.
Okay, hit the road, Jack!
No, no, no!
A lot of brain,
but not enough brawn.
Oh, that was fun!
Cheers!
Well done, my boy.
Um...
No, is it supposed
to taste like that?
No, it is not.
What the hell
is going on?
Okay,
come pick them up!
- Come on.
- Come on out.
Ladies and gentlemen...
The horsemen!
No, you should feel pretty
good about yourself, man.
You predicted it correctly.
The thames,
stroke of midnight.
New year's Eve.
Happy new year!
We are moving now.
The whole thing just changed.
All backup into position stat!
We're on the move.
You're staying here!
Of course.
Move! Move!
Out of the way!
Wow!
Thank you very much, London!
We would like to acknowledge
not just our old friend
but his young and very
brilliant son, Walter mabry.
Who has performed one of the
greatest feats of illusion
even we have ever seen.
He has, amazingly, brought
himself back from the dead!
But before he did that,
he revealed someone.
And we think it
only right to give him
a proper introduction.
He is our friend
and he is our leader.
Dylan shrike!
- Get over here!
- Yeah!
So, normally
only the magician,
his assistant, and
a few trusted stage hands
know the secret
of a trick.
But tonight,
however, in this effect,
all of you people
around the thames here.
And since we're
streaming live,
everyone around the world
already knows everything.
And only these fellows
here are the ones
left in the dark.
So let's see how closely
you were watching our shows.
Remember when we were
playing "find the lady."
I said that we
used a Barry trap.
Some classic switches
and a few duplicates?
Well, that's how we switched
the driver of the truck.
Which took us to
a duplicate hangar
where we used
your need to rush,
and your fear of being seen
let you do the work for us.
Get those lights off me!
So, the airplane.
How did we get it to fly?
Well, we used fans,
and lights and rain machines.
Obviously, all of this was
reliant on us getting caught.
That you would do exactly
what we needed you to do
once you did catch us.
My brother chase,
who was technical adviser
to the losing team.
He taught us that it's
all about blind spots.
I know where you're going!
And, uh, surprises.
Watch it, hobo.
Why don't you watch
the watch I'm wearing,
the where of where
you're watching, and sleep!
It's going to be your idea
to throw the horsemen
out of the plane.
If all of this is
kind of confusing to you,
I can maybe catch
you up on it later.
Probably see you what,
three to five?
Come on, put it there.
Hey! Tit for tat, bro!
Basically,
we showed them everything.
To steal the very thing that
is in your pocket right now.
Whoops!
You know,
this thing here,
which you said
you could use
to adjust markets,
manipulate governments,
also, you could, as you
said control the public
from outside the grid.
These men destroy
people's lives.
Spying on the world,
robbing you of your
right to privacy.
And they do that
by hiding in the dark.
So, in the horsemen tradition,
we're here to expose them.
Tonight, they,
like all of us,
are finally stepping
into the light.
We are the horsemen
and we will be back very soon!
Five, four, three,
two, one!
Hey, we're on the clock.
Get a move on.
There's more inside.
Don't you bloody touch me!
The horsemen are
over on the...
Oh, shit!
Stay with them!
Everybody spread out!
Nobody leaves this barge!
Rhodes,
hold it right there!
Do not move!
This contains everything.
Not just Walter and tressler,
but all their dealings.
All their contacts,
the entire network.
And why on earth
would I believe you?
I told you.
I'm the same man
I've always been.
Move it! Come on!
Let's go, go, go!
I'm not part of this
organization! I'm merritt.
I'm a patsy!
10 minutes.
Now you're playing
the long game.
Dad, I promise
you I will fix this.
You can't.
Stop calling me dad.
There were so many women,
i have no idea
whose bastard you are.
What happened?
Thin air, gone.
Come with me.
What're you talking
about, gone?
People don't
just disappear.
You realize that
he doesn't actually
have magical powers!
Hey, guys.
Hey!
Good to see you all.
Good to see you, li.
Come on in.
Good morning.
Welcome.
I'm proud of you.
All of you.
I have a lot to show you.
Come.
Dad.
Yes.
Your father and i
were partners.
Our act was
that of rivals.
I was the
hard-eyed realist.
He was the
dreamy-eyed idealist.
We thought it was
the perfect misdirect.
Yes, in public,
i did goad him.
The only thing
we didn't count on
was it going so wrong.
Why?
Why didn't you ever
say anything to me?
I don't know.
Give it a name.
Shame, guilt.
Regret.
Hey, guys, uh,
you might wanna come
take a look at this.
Hmm.
Look.
I put you
in jail, man.
Why didn't you
say something then?
Well, you know,
i was going to.
But then, you were
so quick to show your
personal motivations that...
Well, quite frankly
it spoiled
the trick for me.
I showed my weakness.
Well, it showed
you weren't ready.
But when you came
back to my cell,
you had let go of your
30-year vendetta against me
for your horsemen.
And I said to myself,
"that's Lionel's boy."
And I knew it was my job
to see to it that
he became the magician
he was born to be.
All that was
left then was...
For me to hit bottom.
So the safe,
my father's wristwatch,
that was all you?
Walter and tressler,
were they in on it too?
Oh, we knew
Walter was in hiding.
The octa show was a setup
to expose him to the public.
And you were right
about the horsemen.
They needed to learn
to work together like
a single organism.
Now I know why
you look so familiar.
You're the horsemen,
aren't you?
But that can't be
what all this is about.
You know,
the best tricks
work on many levels.
And the deepest one,
for me, at least,
is this moment
right here.
I'm sorry, Dylan.
I miss your father.
30 years is a long time
to drag something
around, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
So, now what?
Now I'm about
out of moves.
Oh...
Come on, you're the one
who said that you
believe that this road
lead to the great wizard
behind the curtain.
And that you'd finally
get to look him in the eyes.
I am.
It's your game now.
You play it however
you see fit.
My suggestion, however,
is that you find
yourself a successor.
Hi. Okay, so, um...
Well, obviously,
we have a few questions.
Right?
Uh... by "a few,"
i think he means,
like, five million.
Yeah.
Well.
Good luck to you all.
What!
Okay. See,
that's not fair.
Come on.
That's not right.
That's gonna make
me really angry!
Not right now.
Oh, um,
by the way...
Pay no attention
to the curtain.
There is a curtain.
Go, go, go.
Seeing is believing.
But is it truth?
Depends on your point of view.
Are you listening, horsemen?
When you emerge,
and you will,
I will be there waiting.
Because mark my words,
you will get
what's coming to you
in ways you can't expect.
But very much deserve.
Because one thing I believe in
is an eye
for an eye.